<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-03-14T17:52:45+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Clwb Mynydda Clwyd</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Social Media</title><link href="/club-info/social/2021/03/13/social-media.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Social Media" /><published>2021-03-13T12:20:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-03-13T12:20:00+00:00</updated><id>/club-info/social/2021/03/13/social-media</id><content type="html" xml:base="/club-info/social/2021/03/13/social-media.html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;club-social-tools&quot;&gt;Club Social Tools&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The social and communal side of the the club is very important! 
CMC uses a number of social media and web apps to communicate with each other.
Some are publicly visible; others are closed to the club members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This page is heavily under review, while we whittle down to the tool that suits us best!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;open-to-the-public&quot;&gt;Open to the public&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have a public information website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://clwyd.clubmesh.com/&quot;&gt;Clubmesh&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/&quot;&gt;This website!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://clwydmountaineeringclub.wordpress.com/&quot;&gt;WordPress&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://hobdellstephen.wixsite.com/clwydmc&quot;&gt;Wix&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;Squarespace&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;closed-to-membership-only&quot;&gt;Closed to membership only&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The tools listed in this section are closed to the club members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;discussion&quot;&gt;Discussion&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We use &lt;em&gt;discussion platform&lt;/em&gt; to discuss our meets, outings, mountaineering, and other topics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://clwyd.clubmesh.com/forums/&quot;&gt;Clubmesh Forum&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/groups/333375560348448&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.facebook.katana&amp;amp;hl=en_GB&amp;amp;gl=US&quot;&gt;Android&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.apple.com/gb/app/facebook/id284882215&quot;&gt;iOS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://app.slack.com/client/T01PNL50LJZ/C01PRVCTE2F&quot;&gt;slack&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.Slack&amp;amp;hl=en_GB&amp;amp;gl=US&quot;&gt;Android&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.apple.com/us/app/slack/id618783545&quot;&gt;iOS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/CMC_Cymru_UK/&quot;&gt;reddit&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.reddit.frontpage&amp;amp;hl=en_GB&amp;amp;gl=US&quot;&gt;Android&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.apple.com/us/app/reddit/id1064216828&quot;&gt;iOS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://discord.com/channels/817725344656261130/817725344656261133&quot;&gt;discord&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.discord&amp;amp;hl=en_GB&amp;amp;gl=US&quot;&gt;Android&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.apple.com/us/app/discord-talk-chat-hang-out/id985746746&quot;&gt;iOS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://groups.google.com/g/clwydmountaineeringclub&quot;&gt;Google Groups&lt;/a&gt; - web only, but works on android/iOS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;messaging-apps-for-last-minute-organisation&quot;&gt;Messaging apps for last-minute organisation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We use &lt;em&gt;messaging app&lt;/em&gt; to keep in touch for events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Telegram - &lt;a href=&quot;https://web.telegram.org/&quot;&gt;Web&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=org.telegram.messenger&amp;amp;hl=en_GB&amp;amp;gl=US&quot;&gt;Android&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.apple.com/us/app/telegram-messenger/id686449807&quot;&gt;iOS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;WhatsApp - &lt;a href=&quot;https://web.whatsapp.com/&quot;&gt;Web&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.whatsapp&amp;amp;hl=en_GB&amp;amp;gl=US&quot;&gt;Android&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.apple.com/us/app/whatsapp-messenger/id310633997&quot;&gt;iOS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Facebook Messenger - &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.messenger.com/&quot;&gt;Web&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.facebook.orca&amp;amp;hl=en_GB&amp;amp;gl=US&quot;&gt;Android&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.apple.com/us/app/messenger/id454638411&quot;&gt;iOS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;club-and-committee-meetings&quot;&gt;Club and Committee Meetings&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Committee and AGMs are held on&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Zoom&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Slack&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Microsoft Teams&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Facebook Rooms?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Club-Info" /><category term="Social" /><category term="social" /><category term="communication" /><category term="connecting" /><summary type="html">Club Social Tools</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Club Trips</title><link href="/club-info/club-trips/2021/03/07/club-trips.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Club Trips" /><published>2021-03-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-03-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/club-info/club-trips/2021/03/07/club-trips</id><content type="html" xml:base="/club-info/club-trips/2021/03/07/club-trips.html">&lt;p&gt;Throughout the year there are many club trips organised by members to venues in the UK and abroad. These are posted on the meets section of the website and in “The Clwydian” and include walking, mountaineering and rock climbing. They are only open to fully paid up members.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Club-Info" /><category term="Club-Trips" /><category term="club-trips" /><summary type="html">Throughout the year there are many club trips organised by members to venues in the UK and abroad. These are posted on the meets section of the website and in “The Clwydian” and include walking, mountaineering and rock climbing. They are only open to fully paid up members.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Clwyd Rock Meets</title><link href="/club-info/climbing/2021/03/07/clwyd-rock-meets.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Clwyd Rock Meets" /><published>2021-03-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-03-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/club-info/climbing/2021/03/07/clwyd-rock-meets</id><content type="html" xml:base="/club-info/climbing/2021/03/07/clwyd-rock-meets.html">&lt;p&gt;The Thursday Evening Clwyd Rock meets are open to all current and prospective members. The venues are chosen to suit all grades of climbing ability and are spread across the area to give all a reasonable opportunity after work. They give a good mix of Trad and Sport climbing with some Bouldering when evenings are short and usually start from 6.00-6.30pm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Details will appear in the club calendar and forum on the week of each meet. If bad weather is forecast with enough warning, then an indoor venue might be suggested on the forums. Post any questions on the forums initially or contact Rod Lloyd-Jones on 01978 820052.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One harness &amp;amp; helmet may be available on loan for new starters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For details of venues and directions, see the local guidebook “Clwyd Rock” by Rockfax or UKC website.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Club-Info" /><category term="Climbing" /><category term="climbing" /><summary type="html">The Thursday Evening Clwyd Rock meets are open to all current and prospective members. The venues are chosen to suit all grades of climbing ability and are spread across the area to give all a reasonable opportunity after work. They give a good mix of Trad and Sport climbing with some Bouldering when evenings are short and usually start from 6.00-6.30pm.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Planning Guidelines &amp;amp; Cancellation</title><link href="/club-info/club-trips/2021/03/07/planning-guidelines-cancellation-policy.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Planning Guidelines &amp;amp; Cancellation" /><published>2021-03-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-03-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/club-info/club-trips/2021/03/07/planning-guidelines-cancellation-policy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/club-info/club-trips/2021/03/07/planning-guidelines-cancellation-policy.html">&lt;p&gt;Any member can organise a trip or event. However, if you want to ask the club to consider covering some financial outlay (say a hut booking) then you are expected to have planned far enough in advance to place your item on the next committee meeting agenda (approximately every 3 months).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Try to judge enthusiasm and know how much the trip will cost. Possible venue suggestions:
Camping.
Cwm Glas Mawr hut in LLanberis Pass (£40 per night, sleeps 11 and requires 1 CC member).
Moelwyn Cottage at PyB (£236 per night sleeps 16).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What you bring to the committee would benefit from detail; numbers of people interested, costs, possible dates, how much you want to have underwritten and when any loan would be paid back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Advertise: Use the website forum. Ask the Chair or Secretary to e-mail the membership with information about the event, asking for expressions of interest.
A minimum of 50% deposit must be asked for and the rest of the money 1 month before the trip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To establish a buffer fund where the club has underwritten costs, an extra £1 per person should be charged and the monies given to the club treasurer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone going on a club trip must be a fully paid up member. Check with the membership secretary or the latest Clwydian to confirm the membership status of those interested. Members can bring guests to events such as the annual BBQ, AGM, club dinners and winter slide shows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CMC TRIPS AND EVENTS CANCELLATION POLICY
The following policy applies to members who, having paid their deposit for club trips, then want to cancel. Under those circumstances members will be required to pay their full share of the trip. The reason being that, if they didn’t, their cancellation would result in those remaining, or the club, incurring increased costs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those booking themselves on club events such as the annual BBQ, coaching weekends, and club dinners etc. should pay as soon as possible and will be expected to pay the full cost on cancellation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Anyone who cancels from a trip or event is, of course, free to recruit another member to go in their place and recoup the monies from them perhaps by advertising or selling their place on the club website forum.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Club-Info" /><category term="Club-Trips" /><category term="club-trips" /><summary type="html">Any member can organise a trip or event. However, if you want to ask the club to consider covering some financial outlay (say a hut booking) then you are expected to have planned far enough in advance to place your item on the next committee meeting agenda (approximately every 3 months).</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Climbing Coaching</title><link href="/club-info/climbing/2021/03/07/climbing-coaching.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Climbing Coaching" /><published>2021-03-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-03-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/club-info/climbing/2021/03/07/climbing-coaching</id><content type="html" xml:base="/club-info/climbing/2021/03/07/climbing-coaching.html">&lt;p&gt;For those that are keen to improve their climbing grade, Clwyd MC offers climbing coaching. Normally we have at least one coaching weekend in the year when experienced members offer their services. This year we also had coaches from Plas y Brenin.
The club also offers one-to-one coaching. Several experienced members have kindly offered their services in that regard and can be accessed through contacting Mike Doyle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It should be noted that this is an informal arrangement between members.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Club-Info" /><category term="Climbing" /><category term="climbing" /><summary type="html">For those that are keen to improve their climbing grade, Clwyd MC offers climbing coaching. Normally we have at least one coaching weekend in the year when experienced members offer their services. This year we also had coaches from Plas y Brenin. The club also offers one-to-one coaching. Several experienced members have kindly offered their services in that regard and can be accessed through contacting Mike Doyle.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Climbing</title><link href="/club-info/climbing/2021/03/07/climbing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Climbing" /><published>2021-03-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-03-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/club-info/climbing/2021/03/07/climbing</id><content type="html" xml:base="/club-info/climbing/2021/03/07/climbing.html">&lt;p&gt;Clwyd MC is an active club with climbing meets arranged every Sunday all year round.
Mid-week we have meets on Tuesday and Wednesday evenings when the days are longer. These are currently the coastal rock meets on a Tuesday evening which includes all the crags along the A55 corridor as far as Penmaenmawr and including the Ormes.
On Wednesday evenings it’s the Clwyd rock area meets which include the inland crags near Llangollen. These also take in Maesafn and Pothole Quarry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The meets are posted on the website during the previous week, and members may also contact the meets co-ordinator by e-mail or phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Sunday meets are normally held in Snowdonia and have included Llanberis Pass, Milestone Buttress, Idwal Slabs and y Moelwynion in the past year.
In addition members arrange to meet informally at weekends or during the week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hold regular weekend coaching meets for beginners as well as those wanting to improve their climbing. The coaches are more experienced members of the club. These meets are usually based in the Cwm Glas Mawr hut in Llanberis Pass and are a good opportunity, especially for those new to the club, to socialise with other members. Individual coaching can also be arranged.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Away meets are organised both in the UK and abroad. Most years we have a weekend at the Roaches, staying in the Don Whillans hut and a week sport climbing in Portland as well as trips to the Alps. ‘Hot Rock’ sport climbing winter meets have included trips to Italy, Turkey, Kalymnos, Sardinia, Morocco and Spain. More details of these events are given in the meets section.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Club-Info" /><category term="Climbing" /><category term="climbing" /><summary type="html">Clwyd MC is an active club with climbing meets arranged every Sunday all year round. Mid-week we have meets on Tuesday and Wednesday evenings when the days are longer. These are currently the coastal rock meets on a Tuesday evening which includes all the crags along the A55 corridor as far as Penmaenmawr and including the Ormes. On Wednesday evenings it’s the Clwyd rock area meets which include the inland crags near Llangollen. These also take in Maesafn and Pothole Quarry.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Club History</title><link href="/club-info/about/2021/03/07/club-history.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Club History" /><published>2021-03-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-03-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/club-info/about/2021/03/07/club-history</id><content type="html" xml:base="/club-info/about/2021/03/07/club-history.html">&lt;p&gt;Clwyd Mountaineering Club began its life as Denbighshire Mountaineering Club in 1969. The Club was formed by a small, active group of climbers of generally average ability, who wanted to establish a circle of friends with whom they could climb or walk in the hills regularly. In 1975, with the change of the County name, the Club became Clwyd Mountaineering Club. From these modest beginnings, the Club has grown and developed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The club membership is typically between 100 and 200 members with climbing at standards ranging from V.Diff to E4. There are experienced mountaineers with up to 40 years of knowledge to call on, grade IV winter climbers, as well as more modest performers. Members tend to be multi-disciplinary and many forms of mountain activity are pursued from mountaineering and scrambling to ice and rock climbing at all grades. The relatively small membership and breadth of activity ensures that we remain a vibrant and friendly club.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This framework generates discussion and encouragement, an integral part of a climber’s life. We have a membership of a variety of ages and abilities. We are one of the few local clubs to welcome novices, and we run regular training events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In recent years some members have been heavily involved in new routing, crag development and guide book work. These have focused on local crags along the A55 corridor, particularly Penmaen Head, Llanddulas Cave and Castle Inn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clwyd MC is active with the BMC, via the Committee for Wales, and is also affiliated to the Snowdonia National Park Society. We help and advise on local access problems, and helping larger organisations with campaigning on many subjects, mainly related to mountain conservation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is Club policy to encourage and promote safe mountaineering (insofar as this is possible). Prospective Members should realise that there are risks in mountain sports, and you will be asked to sign a waiver accordingly when you complete your Membership Application Form. The Club cannot accept liability for any accident, however caused.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Club-Info" /><category term="About" /><category term="about" /><summary type="html">Clwyd Mountaineering Club began its life as Denbighshire Mountaineering Club in 1969. The Club was formed by a small, active group of climbers of generally average ability, who wanted to establish a circle of friends with whom they could climb or walk in the hills regularly. In 1975, with the change of the County name, the Club became Clwyd Mountaineering Club. From these modest beginnings, the Club has grown and developed.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">North Wales Coast Rock Meets</title><link href="/club-info/climbing/2021/03/07/north-wales-coast-rock-meets.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="North Wales Coast Rock Meets" /><published>2021-03-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-03-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/club-info/climbing/2021/03/07/north-wales-coast-rock-meets</id><content type="html" xml:base="/club-info/climbing/2021/03/07/north-wales-coast-rock-meets.html">&lt;p&gt;During the Summer there is a North Wales coast evening rock meet every Tuesday night for a 4 month period from May to August and a different crag will be visited each week. The programme makes full use of the “A55 Sport Climbs” guide book. For Craig-y-Forwyn a free download is available from The Climbers Club website: [http://www.climbers-club.co.uk/downloads/forwyn_lr.pdf]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All welcome including prospective members.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Club-Info" /><category term="Climbing" /><category term="climbing" /><summary type="html">During the Summer there is a North Wales coast evening rock meet every Tuesday night for a 4 month period from May to August and a different crag will be visited each week. The programme makes full use of the “A55 Sport Climbs” guide book. For Craig-y-Forwyn a free download is available from The Climbers Club website: [http://www.climbers-club.co.uk/downloads/forwyn_lr.pdf]</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sunday Rock Meets</title><link href="/club-info/climbing/2021/03/07/sunday-rock-meets.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sunday Rock Meets" /><published>2021-03-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-03-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/club-info/climbing/2021/03/07/sunday-rock-meets</id><content type="html" xml:base="/club-info/climbing/2021/03/07/sunday-rock-meets.html">&lt;p&gt;Martin Worthy is the co-ordinator and will post details of the weekly climbing meet on the club bulletin board.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meets are usually held in Snowdonia on a Sunday and in the past year we have visited (amongst others):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Y Moelwynion
The Idwal Slabs
Milestone Buttress
The Llanberis Pass
There is such a diverse range of climbing in Snowdonia, Martin knows it well and can choose a good location!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Existing and prospective members are welcome to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Club-Info" /><category term="Climbing" /><category term="climbing" /><summary type="html">Martin Worthy is the co-ordinator and will post details of the weekly climbing meet on the club bulletin board.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Committee Members</title><link href="/club-info/about/2021/03/07/committee-members.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Committee Members" /><published>2021-03-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-03-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/club-info/about/2021/03/07/committee-members</id><content type="html" xml:base="/club-info/about/2021/03/07/committee-members.html">&lt;p&gt;Clwyd Mountaineering Club currently has the following committee members:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;chairman&quot;&gt;CHAIRMAN&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peter Friend&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;p.j.friend@icloud.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;vice-chairman&quot;&gt;VICE CHAIRMAN&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mike Burrows&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;michaelburrows@clwydmc.co.uk&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;honorary-secretary&quot;&gt;HONORARY SECRETARY&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jane Kenney&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;janekenney1@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;membership-secretary&quot;&gt;MEMBERSHIP SECRETARY&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paul Ross&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;paulsross@fastmail.fm&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;entertainments-officer&quot;&gt;ENTERTAINMENTS OFFICER&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vacant&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;honorary-treasurer&quot;&gt;HONORARY TREASURER&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alun Ward&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ajwbronnant@hotmail.co.uk&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;journal-editor&quot;&gt;JOURNAL EDITOR&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Steve Debar&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;outdoorsteve@outlook.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;bmc-representative--conservation-officer&quot;&gt;BMC REPRESENTATIVE &amp;amp; CONSERVATION OFFICER&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Steve Hobdell&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;hobdell.stephen@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Club-Info" /><category term="About" /><category term="about" /><summary type="html">Clwyd Mountaineering Club currently has the following committee members:</summary></entry></feed>